<quotations>

	<quotation level="1" author="Anonymous">
	all programs have bugs.
	</quotation>

	<quotation level="2" author="Goethe">
	We only see what we know.
	</quotation>
	
	<quotation level="3" author="">
	You won't make it this way.
	</quotation>
	
	
	<quotation level="4" author="Dejan Stojanovic">
	Fly without wings; Dream with open eyes; See in darkness.
	</quotation>

	
	<quotation level="5" author="Anonymous">
	Don’t worry if it doesn’t work right. If everything did, you’d be out of a job.

	</quotation>
	
	<quotation level="6" author="Mary Tyler Moore">
	Take chances, make mistakes. That's how you grow. Pain nourishes your courage. You have to fail in order to practice being brave.
	</quotation>
	
	<quotation level="7" author="">
	Can you see me ?
	</quotation>
	
	<quotation level="8" author="Mark Zuckerberg">
	Move fast, break things.
	</quotation>
	
	<quotation level="9" author="Anonymous">
	Unity is strength, division is weakness.
	</quotation>
	
	<quotation level="10" author="Wayne Dyer">
	If you change the way you look at things, the things you look at change.
	</quotation>
	
	<quotation level="11" author="">
	Are you sure that way ?
	</quotation>
	
	<quotation level="12" author="">
	Left or right ?.
	</quotation>
	
	<quotation level="13" author="Dennie van Tassel">
	I’ve finally learned what ‘upward compatible’ means.  It means we get to keep all our old mistakes.
	</quotation>
	
	<quotation level="14" author="Assaad Chalhoub">
	Let he who has a bug free software cast the first stone.
	</quotation>
	
	<quotation level="15" author="">
	This bug is so annoying!
	</quotation>
	
	<quotation level="16" author="Rich Kulawiec">
	Any sufficiently advanced bug is indistinguishable from a feature.
	</quotation>
	
	<quotation level="17" author="">
	If something doesn't work as expected, just turn it off !
	</quotation>
	
	<quotation level="18" author="Alan J. Perlis">
	There are two ways to write error-free programs; only the third one works.
	</quotation>
	
	<quotation level="19" author="Anonymous">
	If at first you don't succeed, call it version 1.0
	</quotation>
	
	<quotation level="20" author="Dan Salomon">
	Sometimes it pays to stay in bed in Monday, rather than spending the rest of the week debuging Monday's code.
	</quotation>

	
	<quotation level="21" author="">
	Do it again. Never give up !
	</quotation>

	<quotation level="22" author="Anonymous">
	If anything can go wrong, it will go wrong.
	</quotation>

	<quotation level="23" author="Alan Cohen">
	Do not wait until the conditions are perfect to begin. Beginning makes the conditions perfect.
	</quotation>

	<quotation level="24" author="James Thurber">
	A pinch of probability is worth a pound of perhaps.
	</quotation>
	
	<quotation level="25" author="">
	Do not panic your phone will be fine XD.
	</quotation>

	<quotation level="26" author="Yogi Berra">
	You can see a lot by just looking.
	</quotation>

	<quotation level="27" author="Mandy Hale">
	Sometimes it takes a wrong turn to get you to the right place.
	</quotation>

	<quotation level="28" author="R.Collier">
	Success is the sum of small efforts, repeated day in and day out.
	</quotation>

	<quotation level="29" author="James Thurber">
	If you can't do it by yourself why don't you ask someone else to do it for you ?
	</quotation>

	<quotation level="30" author="Vidiu Platon">
	I don’t care if it works on your machine!  We are not shipping your machine!
	</quotation>

</quotations>
